# Arifur Rahman Arif

### Full Stack Web Developer

Confident and positive minded individual with great communication and interpersonal skills who recently graduated an one year full-time training in Full stack Web Development with programming skills in JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3 and NodeJS. Curious about new technologies and looking for a new challenge within the digital industry.

ararif.aa@gmail.com

+4917621649289

Berlin, Germany

in linkedin.com/in/arifur-rahman-arif-416735131

github.com/arifur-ra

#### **EDUCATION BACKGROUND**

## Full Stack Wed Developer

DCI-Digital Career Institute gGmbH

07/2020 - Present

Berlin, Germany

Courses

- Accomplishing a one-year-full-time training including technologies from MERN stack
- Completing multiple small and one final large practical project to practice programming skills
- Taking German lesson as part of course in level B2

## **Bsc in Computer Sceince**

## Stamford University Bangladesh

09/2007 - 05/2012

Dhaka, Bangladesh

Courses

- o Completed 4 years Bachelor degree with Final Thesis
- Evaluation of the Quality of Voice Over Internet Protocol (VOIP)
  Service with respect to Varying Encoding Techniques
- Graduating with a GPA of 3.57

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Sales Man

#### **Galeries Lafayette**

06/2018 - 04/2020

Tasks

• Showcased product features to customers and discussed technical details to overcome objections and lock in sales.

## Service Staff (Waiter)

#### Gasthaus Gottlob

01/2015 - 05/2018

Tasks

 Providing excellent wait service to ensure satisfaction. Taking coustomer orders and delivering food and beverages. Making menu recommendations, answering questions and sharing additional information with restaurant patrons.

#### **SKILLS**



#### RELEVANT PROJECT

Sell Your Records (02/2021 - Present)

- E-commerce Web Application
- Its all about music, people can buy and sell all kind of music form this platform.
- Technologies used: React, Java Script, HTML, NodeJS, ExpressJs, Materials-UI, BongoDB

#### Simple To-Do-App (12/2020 - 01/2021)

- Simple Adding and Deleting the List
- Technologies used: React, JavaScript, CSS, HTML

#### **LANGUAGES**

#### English

Professional Working Proficiency

#### German

Limited Working Proficiency

#### Bangla

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### **HOBBIES**

I would like to Play Badminton, Cricket & Billiards.

I would like to travel around the world.